Guide to the Biographical Reference Collection, 1972-2004 UA.01.11.0004
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Biographical Files
  - Ward, Charles E. [English] (Box 26)
  - Ward, James A. [Architect] (Box 26)
  - Ward, Robert [Music] (Box 26)
  - Wardell, Lewis (Box 26)
  - Warner, Seth [Mathematics] (Box 26)
  - Washington, Booker T. [Visitor, 1896] (Box 26)
  - Wasiolek, Sue [Student Life] (Box 26)
  - Waters, Bucky [Basketball] (Box 26)
  - Watson, K. Brantley (Box 26)
  - Watson, Richard [History] (Box 26)
  - Watson-Borden, Peggy (Box 26)
  - Watts, George Washington (Box 26)
  - Way, Katharine [Physics] (Box 26)
  - Weatherspoon, Everett B. [Administration] (Box 26)
  - Webb, Albert M. [Romance Languages] (Box 26)
  - Weeks, Stephen B. (Box 26)
  - Weistart, John (Box 26)
  - Weitz, Henry [Education; University Counseling Center] (Box 26)
  - Weldon, Wilson O. [Divinity School] (Box 26)
  - Weller, Henry R. [Physics] (Box 26)
  - Wells, Richard L. [Chemistry] (Box 26)
  - West, Henry Carson (Box 26)
  - Westerhoff, John H., III [Divinity School] (Box 26)
  - Wetherby, Joseph C. [English; Debate Team] (Box 26)
  - Wetmore, Evans (Box 26)
  - Whanger, Alan [Psychiatry] (Box 26)
  - Wharton, Annabel (Box 26)
  - White, Julius Irvan [Sept. of Construction- Duke Chapel] (Box 26)
  - White, Nathaniel [1 of the first 5 African American graduates] (Box 26)
  - White, Newman Ivey (Box 26)
  - White, Richard A. [Botany; Trinity Dean] (Box 26)
  - White, Suzanne [Dance] (Box 26)
  - Whitford, William Edward [Operations and Maintenance] (Box 26)
  - Whitted, Richard (Box 26)
  - Whittington, Erma [Head, Jay B. Hubbell Center] (Box 26)
  - Widgery, Alban G. [Pholosophy] (Box 26)
  - Widman, Mary Anne [Golf] (Box 26)
  - Wilbur, Karl [Zoology] (Box 26)
  - Wilder, Pelham [Chemistry; University Marshall] (Box 26)
  - Wilkie, Wendell L. (Box 26)
  - Wilkinson, Howard Charles [Chaplain to the University] (Box 26)
  - Wilkinson, Jay [Football] (Box 26)
  - Williams, Doris [West Campus Dining] (Box 26)
  - Williams, George Walton [English] (Box 26)
  - Williams, Kenny J. [English] (Box 26)
  - Williams, Leland H. [President, Triangle Computation Center] (Box 26)
  - Williams, Mary Lou [Music] (Box 26)
  - Williams, Neil (Box 26)
  - Williams, Patrick (Box 26)
  - Williams, Peter F. [Music] (Box 26)
  - Williams, R. Sanders "Sandy" [Dean, Medical School] (Box 27)
  - Willimon, William H. [Divinity School] (Box 27)
  - Willis, William H. [Greek] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Barry [Football] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, James F. [Engineering] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Mary Grace [Woman's College] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Robert L. [Divinity School] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Robert North [Chemistry] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Shirley "Red" [Football] (Box 27)
  - Wilson, Tom [Engineering] (Box 27)
  - Winfree, Robert G. [DUMC] (Box 27)
  - Wise, Thomas James (Box 27)
  - Wissoker, Kenneth [Duke Press] (Box 27)
  - Withers, Loren [Music] (Box 27)
  - Witt, Ronald G. [History] (Box 27)
  - Wolfe, James J. [Duke's first botanist] (Box 27)
  - Womble, Bunyan Snipes [Trustee] (Box 27)
  - Wood, Marquis Lafayette (Box 27)
  - Wood, Peter H. [History] (Box 27)
  - Woodhall, Barnes [Neurosurgery] (Box 27)
  - Woodruff, Judy [Alumnae; Trustee] (Box 27)
  - Woody, Robert H. [History] (Box 27)
  - Wright, Richard Harvey (Box 27)
  - Wyngaarden, James [Medicine] (Box 27)
  - Wynkoop, Rodney [Music director, Duke Chapel] (Box 27)
  - Ybara, Gary [Engineering] (Box 27)
  - Yeager, Robert C. (Box 27)
  - Yoh, Harold [Trustee] (Box 27)
  - Yohe, William [Economics] (Box 27)
  - York, Brantley (Box 27)
  - Young, Betty [Woman's College Library] (Box 27)
  - Young, Paul [Director, Chapel Choir] (Box 27)
  - Young, Robert T. [Chaplain to the University] (Box 27)
  - Younger, John G. [Classical Studies] (Box 27)
  - Zener, Karl Edward [Psychology] (Box 27)
  - Zimmerman, Matthew A., Jr. (Box 27)
  - Terry Sanford Clippings (primarily Duke years) (Box 28)
  - Terry Sanford Clippings (primarily political) (Box 29)
  - Terry Sanford Clippings, circa 1965-1990 (Box 30)